{
  "title": "Japanese Phrases Mastery Challenge",
  "description": "Take on the challenge of mastering Japanese phrases with this quiz. Featuring nuanced greetings, expressions of gratitude, and complex questions, each item offers options, a hint, and the correct answer in Japanese characters and Romaji. Test your proficiency and elevate your Japanese language skills to an advanced level!",
    "items": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How do you greet someone during the day?",
        "answer": "こんにちは",
        "options": ["さようなら", "ありがとう", "すみません", "こんにちは"],
        "hint": "Common greeting"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What expression is used to show gratitude or say 'thank you'?",
        "answer": "ありがとう",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "こんにちは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Expressing gratitude"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'yes'?",
        "answer": "はい",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "こんにちは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Affirmative response"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How do you say 'no' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "いいえ",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "こんにちは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Negative response"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which phrase is used as a morning greeting?",
        "answer": "おはようございます",
        "options": ["こんばんは", "こんにちは", "おはようございます", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Morning greeting"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What phrase is used to greet someone in the evening?",
        "answer": "こんばんは",
        "options": ["おはようございます", "こんにちは", "こんばんは", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Evening greeting"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How do you apologize or get someone's attention in Japanese?",
        "answer": "すみません",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "すみません", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Apology or seeking attention"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What is the common way to ask 'How are you?' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "お元気ですか",
        "options": ["さようなら", "お元気ですか", "すみません", "ありがとう"],
        "hint": "Asking about well-being"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "How do you express appreciation for someone's hard work in Japanese?",
        "answer": "お疲れ様です",
        "options": ["はい", "お疲れ様です", "すみません", "こんにちは"],
        "hint": "Common expression in the workplace"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What question would you ask when you want to know what something is?",
        "answer": "これは何ですか",
        "options": ["はい", "いいえ", "これは何ですか", "こんにちは"],
        "hint": "Asking about an object"
      }
    ]
  }
  